<resources>
    <!--
      Copyright 2020 The Android Open Source Project
      Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except
      in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
      Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License
      is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express
      or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under
      the License.
      -->
    <string name="app_name">AndroidDevChallenge</string>
    <string name="charlie_description">Charlie is a super smart amazing dog with so much love to give. Charlie is well trained knows all commands sit, heal, go to your bed, stay on your bed, go to your crate, paw he knows it all. Charlie is very protective and so loving he needs a experienced owner who keeps her in check and loves him. He loves to play with toys she is a great fetcher and will be the most loyal dog you will ever know. We require that you meet with our trainer and that you take 15 training sessions with our trainer. You will love our trainer he has been training for 30 years. Give Charlie a chance to be your forever best friend. He was abandoned and given up and hit in the face and he has come through it all.</string>
    <string name="sally_description">Hello, my name is Tink! I was rescued from the shelter in honor of a dog who suffered a horrible fate there. I love people, but dont get along with most dogs. I am about 3 years old and looking for my forever family. If you think that is you please contact Ace of Hearts so we can meet!</string>
    <string name="molly_description">This little nugget had a rough start in life.. she came to us with dreadlocks! Needs a special, savvy and understanding person to love her and respect her needs. She does not like to be picked up!!!!! She wags his tail all the time and plays with toys for hours. She’s pretty funny and entertaining. She has improved tremendously from her training and is so much friendlier but still acts out. Loves long walks. Knows basic commands. Still must be careful handling her. She is sensitive and can be unpredictable. Needs very experienced adopter and a garden is ideal so she can potty when she wants. No children! Best in a home with a dog door and years of enclosed patio.</string>
    <string name="males_description">Males was found as a stray by her foster, she is aprox. 1 year old, very playful, and will be the perfect fit for an active family who is available to continue her puppy training.</string>
    <string name="rosie_description">Rosie was found as a stray injured when he was attached by another dog. Edison does not get along well with other dogs, would do great as a single dog in a home. Very cautious when first meeting, but a love bug and very obedient. He knows sit and stays with you with no reaction towards other dogs except being cautious with males because of his experience. He is been coming out of his shell very nicely, wagging his tail and walking great on a leash. His foster says that he is just the best and will make a wonderful forever friend to some lucky adopter. Who knows, that could be you!</string>
    <string name="bigben_description">Big Ben is a big dog with a big heart. He loves his people and is a goofy guy. He is 10 years old and has some old dog arthritis that he is getting medication for. But don not let that fool you he is still energetic and strong and would do best with someone who is comfortable handling a large strong dog. Big Ben needs to be the only animal in the home. He will give your tons of love and attention, so he’ll be all you need. He is full of personality and will bring joy to his new family.</string>
    <string name="loyalty_description">Loyalty is Momma-bear to a litter of pups we brought up last Summer. She is chalk full of energy and needs an experienced home with people who have plenty of time to dedicate! She is extremely smart and loves her people.</string>
</resources>